Yujian 'Charles' Tang

University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill yujian@live.unc.edu • Phone: (919) 741-4667

RESEARCH INTERESTS

My current research topic is on training neural networks to learn the segmentation of subcortical structures in macaque brains using deep learning on a convolutional neural network. Previous research experience includes image processing in neuroimaging, and data cleaning for mobile crowdsensing. I hope to do research on modeling human behavior in the real world in the future.

EDUCATION

University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill (Expected)

Chapel Hill, NC August 2015-May 2019

B.S., Computer Science Minors: Statistics, Neuroscience

PRESENTATIONS, PRECEDINGS, AND PAPERS

Tang, Y., Tasnim, S., Pissinou, N., Iyengar, S. S., & Shahid, A. (2018). Reputation-Aware Data Fusion and Malicious Participant Detection in Mobile Crowdsensing. Presentation at IEEE Big Data 2018 (12/13/18)

Aleman, C., Pissinou, N., Alemany, S., & Kamhoua, G. (2018). Using Candlestick Charting and Dynamic Time Warping for Data Behavior Modeling and Trend Prediction for MWSN in IOT. Presentation at IEEE Big Data 2018 (12/10/18)

Tang, Y., Kim, S., & Styner, M. (2018). Adapting the CIVET Pipeline to Rhesus Macaque Brains. Presentation at State of North Carolina Undergraduate Research Symposium (11/10/18)

Tang, Y., Kim, S., & Styner, M. (2018). Adapting the CIVET Pipeline to Macague Brains. Presentation at University of North Carolina Computer Science Research Symposium (4/16/18)

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

Neuro Image Research and Analysis Labs

Chapel Hill, NC

Research Assistant Mentor: Dr. Martin Styner August 2018-Present

Research Experience for Undergraduates, National Science Foundation

Miami, FL May 2018-August 2018

Research Intern

Mentors: Dr. Niki Pissinou, Samia Tasnim

Neuro Image Research and Analysis Labs

Chapel Hill, NC

Research Assistant

June 2017-May 2018

Mentors: Dr. Martin Styner, and Dr. Sun-Hyung Kim

WORK EXPERIENCE

Department of Computer Science, UNC

Chapel Hill, NC Fall 17, Spring 18, Fall 18

Undergraduate Learning Assistant (COMP 283)

Instructor: Dr. David Plaisted

ITS Franklin, UNC

Chapel Hill, NC

June 2017-August 2017 Middleware Intern

Department of Computer Science, UNC

Chapel Hill, NC

Fall 2016

Undergraduate Learning Assistant (COMP 410)

Instructor: Dr. David Stotts

nCino Wilmington, NC

Developer Intern June 2016-August 2016

HONORS
Undergraduate Learning Assistant of the Year Nominee, 2018
NC State Math Contest Scholarship Winner, 2015